
	
		TR 2013/1 INCOME TAX: THE IDENTIFICATION OF
			&ldquo;EMPLOYER&rdquo; FOR THE PURPOSES OF THE SHORT-TERM VISIT EXCEPTION UNDER
			THE INCOME FROM EMPLOYMENT ARTICLE, OR ITS EQUIVALENT, OF AUSTRALIA&rsquo;S
			TAX TREATIES (TR 2013/1)
		
			
				Related Releases:
				
				TR 2001/13
				;
				
				TR 2005/16
				;
				
				SGR 2005/1
				;
				
				SGR 2005/2
				; TR 2003/11 (withdrawn); issued in draft form as TR 2012/D4.
			
			
			
			
				Income tax &mdash; International &mdash; Double tax agreements &mdash;
					Employment of non-residents &mdash; Employment Article &mdash; General rule
					that employment income taxed by state in which services are
					rendered &mdash; Short-term visit exception to general rule.
			
			
			
			
			
			
			
			
				&bull; This publication provides you with the following level of
					protection:
			
		
		
			
			
			
			
			
				
					
				
				
					
						
							ITAA 1997 8-1
							
							ITAA 1997 Part 2-42
							
							
								Convention between Australia and Canada for the avoidance of
								double taxation and the prevention of fiscal evasion with
								respect to taxes on income
								
								[1981] ATS 14, as amended by the
								Canadian protocol (No. 1)
								
								[2002] ATS 26 (Canadian convention)
							
						
					
				
			
			
			
			
				
					
					
				
				
					
						
							Contents
						
					
				
				
					
						
							LEGALLY BINDING SECTION:
						
					
				
				
					
						
							What this Ruling is about
						
					
					
						
							1
						
					
				
				
					
						
							Previous Ruling
						
					
					
						
							4
						
					
				
				
					
						
							Ruling
						
					
					
						
							5
						
					
				
				
					
						
							Examples
						
					
					
						
							17
						
					
				
				
					
						
							Date of effect
						
					
					
						
							50
						
					
				
				
					
						
							NOT LEGALLY BINDING SECTION:
						
					
				
				
					
						
							Appendix 1:
						
					
				
				
					
						
							
								Explanation
							
						
					
					
						
							51
						
					
				
				
					
						
							Appendix 2:
						
					
				
				
					
						
							
								Glossary of terms
							
						
					
					
						
							131
						
					
				
				
					
						
							Appendix 3:
						
					
				
				
					
						
							
								Extract from the Commentary to Article 15 of the OECD
									Model
							
						
					
					
						
							132
						
					
				
				
					
						
							Appendix 4:
						
					
				
				
					
						
							
								Detailed contents list
							
						
					
					
						
							133
						
					
				
			
			
			
			
				What this Ruling is about
			
			
			
			
				
			
			1. This Ruling explains: 
			
				
					
						&bull; the meaning of the term &lsquo;employer&rsquo; in the general exclusion
						provision provided under the Income from Employment Article, or
						its equivalent,
						
							
							
							The heading of equivalent Articles in other tax treaties
								vary. Consistent with the heading of Article 15 of the OECD
								Model until it changed in 2000, many such Articles are headed
								&lsquo;Dependent Personal Services&rsquo;, for example, Article 15 of the
								Canadian convention. Others may have no heading at all, for
								example, Article 14 of the German agreement and Article 12 of
								the Singaporean agreement.
							
							
						
						of Australia&rsquo;s tax treaties (&lsquo;short-term visit exception&rsquo;;
						
							
							
							Appendix 2 of this Ruling sets out a glossary for some
								terms used in this Ruling: &lsquo;intermediary&rsquo;, &lsquo;international labour
								hire arrangements&rsquo;, &lsquo;short-term visit exception&rsquo; and &lsquo;user
								enterprise&rsquo;.
							
							
						
						) and
					
				
				
					&bull; the approach to be taken in determining who the employer is
						for the purposes of the short-term visit exception.
				
			
			
			
			
			
			
				
			
			2. This Ruling applies to entities that engage
				non-resident individuals to render services in Australia and to
				those non-resident individuals.
		
	
